(Penny:)Thank you.
I really needed to hear that today.
-Ooh! Brie's ready!
-Yay!
(Leonard:)-Good morning.
-Hello.
(Leonard:)So am I driving you to work,
or are you still mad at me?
(Sheldon:)I'd like a ride.
(Sheldon:)Assuming you actually do
take me to work.
(Leonard:)Where do you think I would take you?
Who knows? You said
you'd be home yesterday,
(Sheldon:)but you came home three days ago.
(Sheldon:)You say you're taking me
to work, but for all I know,
(Sheldon:)I'll end up
in a deserted amusement park.
Or a cornheld maze.
Or a back-alley dog fight.
You tell me.
(Leonard:)I'm going to work.
You can come if you want.
(Stuart:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)By the way, you have
something on your shirt.
(Leonard:)-No, I don't.
-Hurls, doesn't it?